saudia.com 2018-06-18

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting SAUDIA web portal and for reviewing our Privacy Policy.  The intent of this privacy policy is to inform you of what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit our website and how we may use that information.

### Data Collection

Our web servers collect and store all information that your web browser sends when it requests a web page, **including:**

  * Name, domain, and numerical internet address of the "host" computer (that of your Internet Service Provider, not necessarily your personal computer) that you use for Internet access;
  * The date and time when you accessed our site;
  * The Internet address of the web page that you came from;
  * The page requested from our site and the number of characters sent to your computer;
  * The information your web browser software sends as its so-called "User Agent," which typically identifies the browser software and may also indicate the operating system and type of CPU used in your personal computer.

SAUDIA intends to analyze these log files to learn how visitors use the site and what improvements we can make to improve user experience.

### Use of Information

Personal information about users visiting our website will not be collected and used, unless the visitor chooses to provide such information. As a policy, we do not attempt to identify individual users or share any information received with outside parties, with the exception of official and authorized law enforcement investigations, or in cases of suspected attempts to deliberately circumvent our system's security with the intent of gaining unauthorized access or inflict technical damage (e.g. an attack by hackers).

### E-mail

We use personal identifying information sent to us via e-mail to respond to your requests for information or assistance. This includes forwarding your e-mail to other SAUDIA staff better able to handle your requests. We don’t intend to retain or distribute e-mail addresses to outside parties. Information collected through e-mails will be retained as long as necessary to complete our response.

"If, at any time, you prefer not to receive email marketing information from us please follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email."

### Cookies

SAUDIA uses cookies for anonymous visitor tracking. Our web server assigns each visitor a unique numerical ID so that we can determine how many unique visitors visited the site. Personal information based on the numerical IDs are not identified nor collected. Information entered in our inquiry and reservation are not linked or related to the cookie data.

### Security

We will take appropriate steps to protect the personal information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features to safeguard the privacy of your personal information. We invest significant resources to protect your personal information, from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. However, no internet-based site can be 100% secure and we cannot be held responsible for unauthorized or unintended access that is beyond our control.

By using this site, you signify your agreement with SAUDIA Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, revise, add or delete parts of this policy at any time. Your continued use of this website following said possible changes to these terms indicates acceptance of those changes.

Any questions or comments regarding SAUDIA’ Privacy Policy should be directed to us by e-mail at  [webmaster@saudia.com](mailto:webmaster@saudia.com).

**SAUDIA**

**Saudi phone number:** 00966 126860000

**P.O. Box** 620, Jeddah 21231

**Kingdom of Saudi Arabia**

**© Copyright 2017 All rights reserved.**
